<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Sandwich Club 03</string>

    <string name="InternetErrorMessage">Проблема с интернет соединением!</string>

    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Открыть панель навигации</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Закрыть панель навигации</string>
    <string name="title_activity_product">Карточка товара</string>
    <string name="title_activity_profile">Ваш профиль</string>
    <string name="large_text">
        "Material is the metaphor.\n\n"

        "A material metaphor is the unifying theory of a rationalized space and a system of motion."
        "The material is grounded in tactile reality, inspired by the study of paper and ink, yet "
        "technologically advanced and open to imagination and magic.\n"
        "Surfaces and edges of the material provide visual cues that are grounded in reality. The "
        "use of familiar tactile attributes helps users quickly understand affordances. Yet the "
        "flexibility of the material creates new affordances that supercede those in the physical "
        "world, without breaking the rules of physics.\n"
        "The fundamentals of light, surface, and movement are key to conveying how objects move, "
        "interact, and exist in space and in relation to each other. Realistic lighting shows "
        "seams, divides space, and indicates moving parts.\n\n"

        "Bold, graphic, intentional.\n\n"

        "The foundational elements of print based design typography, grids, space, scale, color, "
        "and use of imagery guide visual treatments. These elements do far more than please the "
        "eye. They create hierarchy, meaning, and focus. Deliberate color choices, edge to edge "
        "imagery, large scale typography, and intentional white space create a bold and graphic "
        "interface that immerse the user in the experience.\n"
        "An emphasis on user actions makes core functionality immediately apparent and provides "
        "waypoints for the user.\n\n"
    </string>
    <string name="action_settings">Настройки</string>

    <string name="cancel_text">Отмена</string>

    <string name="dialog_countProduct_title">Введите количество</string>
    <string name="create_order_text">Заказать</string>
    <string name="repeat_order_text">Повторить заказ</string>
    <string name="dialog_create_order_title">Подтверждение заказа</string>
    <string name="dialog_create_order_message">Вы уверены?</string>
    <string name="repeat_order_question_title">Повтор заказа</string>
    <string name="repeat_order_question">Вы хотите повторить заказ?</string>
    <string name="success_order_create_title">Ваш заказ принят!</string>
    <string name="success_order_create_message">Наш менеджер свяжется с Вами для уточнения деталей</string>
    <string name="order_info_text">
        Доставка бесплатная в черте города при заказе от 600 рублей. При заказе до 600 рублей доставка рассчитывается индивидуально, в зависимости от расстояния.
    </string>
    <string name="offer_text">Я подтверждаю своё согласие на хранение и обработку моих персональных данных</string>

    <string name="title_activity_maps">Где мы находимся</string>
    <string name="balloon_text">Ваши любимые бургеры тут!</string>
    <string name="btn_price_text">280 р.</string>
    <string name="btn_weight_text">300 гр.</string>
    <string name="product_name_text">Гамбургер</string>

</resources>
